Hello, I am Deepti, now people welcome to the
video of Das paying tax, it is going to be something
different. Everyone
knows that nowadays every work of the bank is done
through our customer care and you have to
call the customer care for any work.
If you are facing any problem,
you are not able to call regarding your
credit card or your debit
card, then I am going to guide you in this video,
I will directly
call you and show you what you should do
tomorrow. Now, if tomorrow is successful and your
problem gets solved, then
we will go about it. So first let us know
what the problem is, let me tell you the whole story.
Last year, I had made a
debit card transfer from my account in ICC Bank. It happened that
my entire record was lost, that is why
I had to make a transfer. I had done it during
this time in June-July.
After that, I also transferred money from it
using the panel, so
its time was nothing, like
in the Aadhar payment etc., while doing this the money was
transferred, then I tried to make some payment from it through mobile, then
after that I tried to make some payment from it,
then  I tried to print from it, then it happened
that I had got it transferred,
I had read that nothing had happened
that whatever happens in it, then I did
not use it and then it happened that I
decided that I will talk to you and talk to the customer,
well I talked to the customer for two-three years, the phone camera was
not successful yesterday, why it was not successful, I will
tell you what is the bank customer number and
along with that any number from any place, you
can subscribe, watch this video of mine, you will find it
in the last and you will find it
in the description below, it is going to be very useful for you
because we also
search the number, then watch this video and I will
tell you how to remove the mistake, take it, thank you,
for your convenience
we have presented this, my debit
card net is not working,
any report related to it, subscribe now,
I want to activate my work,
activation is not working, I
want to activate my comment of America,
I will one night for
financial help in deactivating your account, subscribe to that card,
like, comment and
appoint on your maximum  I gave it and did that
so I had subscribed but now it is
only for school so I am
very worried as I used to enter that
after that see how I did a
successful like yesterday then you will have to
change the option properly when the
computer asks you will have to
tell them about your problem, you will give the option accordingly
and go there then all these schools will have to go to
activate it
if but there is any other problem then again if there has been any
tampering related to it then
you will have to go there then transfer 1971
then you can solve your problem by talking to them
see this is getting a bit
long but stay with it I mean
[music]
ah
what else we have introduced this for your convenience you can
tell us
that I have some problem related to my credit debit card
my card is not working can you
tell me once again my
debit card is not working
why is it not working I am not able to understand
that they should release their debit card number by entering
their four digit ATM debit card
Or activate and appoint now we
can get your call, make
Ajay the
president busy pirate sir
good afternoon editing if you are making online payment
then its online was
changed to talk to subscribe
last updated on's
prime trick made a bank i mobile you
use, you open it hey let me
finish then go and
what settings in my mobile app, another
video of that my purpose was to explain to you that
now how to click on
customer care only then it is
becoming technological and then how you
click on how to talk this video
problem was this after that and the other so
after that I still did and
subscribe to the other accused and if
you want to download the app to know everything in it
subscribe to this channel
and you will get the link of the video
in the description related to this
if you can send the channel in other videos, if you
like it then you can go and subscribe, if you do
n't like it then don't do it at all, do
n't do it at all, Namaste